<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
  <rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
      <title>donReach Social Tools
      </title>
      <description>Increase your social reach and drive more traffic with our free social tools &amp; widgets.
      </description>
      <link>https://donreach.com</link>
    <atom:link href="https://donreach.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Public social share count API depreciated
]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;The old (keyless) API at &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;count.donreach.com&lt;/code&gt; is of now depreciated and will be
&lt;strong&gt;taken offline&lt;/strong&gt; on the 1. January 2018!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To continue using the API please &lt;a href=&quot;/pricing/&quot;&gt;sign up for a free API key&lt;/a&gt;.
The signup only takes 30 seconds and your API key will be activated instantly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re sorry for any inconvenience caused, but sadly our API is being abused,
using proxy servers to go beyond the set rate-limit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The good news however is that we’re giving away a whopping 15.000 API calls per
day, so the majority of our users won’t be affected and can continue to use our
service &lt;strong&gt;absolutely free!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
On top of that we have upgraded our server infrastructure heavily and rewritten
large parts of the API, making it a ton faster and more reliable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions regarding the switch to the new API, feel free to give
us a shout in the comments below or &lt;a href=&quot;/support/contact/&quot;&gt;open a support ticket&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Happy coding!&lt;/p&gt;
]]></description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://donreach.com/blog/public-api-depreciated/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://donreach.com/blog/public-api-depreciated/</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Celebrate the launch of our new social share count API with a 50% discount!
]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the all new donreach.com. It’s been a while since anything
noteworthy happened here so I’m all the more pleased to break the silence with
not only a flashy new website but also the news most of you have been waiting
for: our premium social share count API has finally launched!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;premium-social-api-launched&quot;&gt;Premium Social API Launched&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Due to ever rising popularity, our open social share count API has been plagued
by bad performance for quite some time now and many of you have asked us for a
long-term solution, so I’m happy to announce our most-requested feature by far:
a lightning fast premium social share count API service with more social
networking services supported than ever!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are some of the highlights:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;get-50-off-for-6-months&quot;&gt;Get 50% off for 6 months&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To celebrate the launch of the new API we’re giving anyone who signs up by the
30th of June a whopping 50% off their first 6 months subscription.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To get the discount simply enter the coupon code &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;LAUNCH50&lt;/code&gt; during checkout.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;improved-performance&quot;&gt;Improved performance&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To cope with the millions of people accessing our API every month we’ve
rewritten it yet again, benchmarking our code at every step of the way to
squeeze out every last bit of performance possible. On top of that, we’re
applying a very generous ratio of premium API users per server to ensure a
reliable service, even during peak-times.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;18-new-social-networking-services-supported&quot;&gt;18 new social networking services supported&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s right, the amount of different social share counts our API can fetch has
nearly doubled! We’ve expanded our portfolio of supported providers to include
major non-english social networks from around the world including China, Russia,
Spain, Poland &amp;amp; Bulgaria, just to name a few.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;follower-counts-beta&quot;&gt;Follower counts (BETA)&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Starting now you can also track social profiles’ follower counts through our
API. This functionality is still in BETA though and likely to change.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more information about our social API check out the following links:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/docs/social-api/reference/&quot;&gt;API Reference&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/pricing/&quot;&gt;Pricing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>https://donreach.com/blog/social-api-premium-launched/</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://donreach.com/blog/social-api-premium-launched/</guid>
  </item>
</channel>
</rss>